https://vodien.com.au/terms/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy aims at the preservation of confidentiality for our customers' information and maintenance of the highest integration for all data presented to Vodien.
The Vodien Internet Solutions website is owned and operated by Dreamscape Networks International Pte Ltd.
Vodien Internet Solutions respects the privacy of each individual that visits our website. Vodien Internet Solutions promises not to disclose personal or business information to third parties without the express permission of You and Your company. We will not sell Your name, e-mail address, phone number, or any other personal information to anyone else. We consider this information to be private, and it will remain as such.
In alignment with Australian regulations,
this privacy statement provides our visitors and customers with information on how Vodien Internet Solutions protects the information supplied.
Information Collection
Information Collection
Vodien Internet Solutions is the sole owner of the information collected on www.vodien.com. Vodien Internet Solutions collects information from our users during the signup process on our Web site.
Signup/Order
We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and billing address). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.
Information Use
Profile
We store information that we collect through cookies and log files to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use session ID cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.
Log Files
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.
WHOIS Directory
Contact information collected for certain top-level domain registrations (e.g. .com) are required by ICANN for the submission to the WHOIS directory. Vodien will also refer to the contact information provided to reach the registrant in cases of issues with the domain names.
Communications from the Site
Special Offers and Updates
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.
Newsletter
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.
Service Announcements
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.
Customer Service
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.
Sharing
Disclosure of Customer Information
Vodien will not disclose its customers' personal information with third parties, with the exception of the following reasons:
To provide service to the registered account user
To cooporate with law enforcement agencies via legal processes such as current judicial proceedings, court orders and warrants that Vodien determines in its sole discretion to be legitimate and compliable
To safeguard the legitimate interests of Vodien and its customers
In any event, whereby Vodien is obliged to disclose customer data in adherence to the served legal process(es), Vodien may disclose any forms of User Information to the respective Law Enforcement Agency without prior consent or notification to the customer. Any interactions between Vodien and the Officials will not be divulged, in order to protect Vodien's legal interests.
Business Transitions
In the event Vodien Internet Solutions goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.
Choice/Opt-out
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by sending us an email at marketing@vodien.com. We also offer an opt-out mechanism on the newsletter subscription confirmation email. Alternatively, the user may contact us at 1300 863 436 to opt-out.
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Vodien Internet Solutions, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postal code). Contact information will be shared with the contest/survey sponsors and used to notify the winners and award prizes. Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users' personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
Advertisements via Third-Party Vendors
Third-party vendors, including Google, show your ads on sites on the internet.
Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. (Alternatively you can point users to opt out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.)
Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as postal code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can be done by emailing our Customer Support at support@vodien.com.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Contact Information
Questions regarding this privacy policy may be directed to contact@vodien.com.
The above stated Privacy Policy is correct as of 6th of April 2018.
Need Help? Call our 24/7 SuperSupport team 1300 863 436
Top
Chat
Phone
Your session is about to expire!
Your session will expire in  minutes.
Click "OK" to extend your session and continue working, or wait to automatically end your session.
OK
Your session has expired!
Your session has expired due to inactivity.Click 'OK' to start to login again.
OK
